https://www.targetmaster.com/privacy-policy

Working...Your cart is emptyItem(s) In Cart0Total$0.00Shipping and taxes calculated at checkoutCheckout BackSign InCreate AccountCheckout as Guest
×
610-459-5400255 Wilmington West Chester Pike Chadds Ford, PA 19317Create AccountSign In
About Us!
About Us
WebSite Item Availability
DRESS CODE & CELL PHONE POLICY!
RANGE
Range Overview / Hours
Membership & Range Rates
Range Rules
GUNS FOR RENT!
Contact Us
Delaware Gun Buyers!
0 0Create AccountSign In
About Us!
About Us
WebSite Item Availability
DRESS CODE & CELL PHONE POLICY!
RANGE
Range Overview / Hours
Membership & Range Rates
Range Rules
GUNS FOR RENT!
Contact Us
Delaware Gun Buyers!
Categories HandgunsOtherRevolversLever ActionSingle ShotSemi-AutomaticDerringerShotgunsPump ActionOver-UnderSide By SideLever ActionSingle ShotSemi-AutomaticBolt ActionAmmoSnap CapsPowdersRifleHandgunShotgunRimfireBulk AmmoSlugsBlanksKnivesAutomaticFixed BladeUtilityFoldingAccessoriesMagazinesAccessoriesHigh CapacityStandardBlack PowderBlack Powder AmmoBlack Powder Accs.Black Powder RiflesBlack Powder HandgunsAccessoriesBody ArmorTargetsSafesBeadsApparelGiftsHolsters / CasesGun CleaningVehicle AccessoriesFirearm AccessoriesGun PartsToolsBagsPublicationsReloading AccessoriesSafety and ProtectionMiscellaneousHuntingDecoysBlindsSpottingCallsFeedersGame ProcessingTrapsScentsAccessoriesRiflesSemi-AutomaticBolt ActionPump ActionCombosTacticalLower ReceiversLever ActionSingle ShotBlack PowderOpticsRangefinderScopesScope MountsSights / Lasers / LightsOptics AccessoriesBinocularsFlashlights / BatteriesSpotting ScopesThermal Scopes
Shop by Category
Handguns
Other
Revolvers
Lever Action
Single Shot
Semi-Automatic
Derringer
Black Powder Ammo
Black Powder Accs.
Black Powder Rifles
Black Powder Handguns
Accessories
Body Armor
Targets
Safes
Beads
Apparel
Targetmaster Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website (Site).
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, Use Live Chat or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
- To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
- To improve our website in order to better serve you.
- To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
- To quickly process your transactions.
- To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
- To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
How do we protect your information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a third-party gateway provider.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
- Allow customers to 'log-in' to the Site.
- Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
- Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If users disable cookies in their browser:
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party technology services
We (the Site) may use third-party technology services. These services may include, but are not limited to the following:
- Ecommerce website service provider(s)
- Payment gateway(s)
- Fraud prevention screening
- Email sending service(s)
- Promotional service(s)
We share your Personal Information with third parties.
Use of Personal Information
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we (or third parties) use this Order Information to:
- Process payments;
- Communicate with you;
- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
- Provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. -
See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
- Users can visit our site anonymously.
- Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
- Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal information:
• By logging in to your account
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control.
The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at targetmaster1@verizon.net
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
255 Wilmington West Chester Pike
Chadds Ford, PA 19317
Phone: 610-459-5400
